Nobody ruins his vacation.
Nobody 2 is a action, thriller film directed by Timo Tjahjanto.
Former assassin Hutch Mansell takes his family on a nostalgic vacation to a small-town theme park, only to be pulled
back into violence when they clash with a corrupt operator, a crooked sheriff, and a ruthless crime boss.
Hutch Mansell, played by Bob Odenkirk.
Becca Mansell, played by Connie Nielsen.
Wyatt Martin, played by John Ortiz.
Sheriff Abel, played by Colin Hanks.
Harry Mansell, played by RZA.
The Barber, played by Colin Salmon.
Nobody (Chinese: 浪浪山小妖怪; pinyin: Làng làng shān xiǎo yāo guài; literally The Little Monster of
Langlang Mountain) is a 2025 Chinese animated fantasy film written and directed by Yu Shui.
It was animated by the Shanghai Animation Film Studio and is based on an
episode of the anthology series Yao-Chinese Folktales.
It is the highest-grossing 2D animated film made by a Chinese company.
The film explores themes of assassin, dark
comedy, sequel, revenge, one man army.
The tone is dark and intense.